Budnik Andrei

E-mail | Linkedin | Github | Telegram

Summary

QA Engineer in the field of web, mobile, DB, API testing. Ability to use a wide variety of tools and the ability to quickly learn new ones and adapt to product and business priorities. Experience working remotely in a distributed team.

Experience

Employee on internship *QA Engineer (remote)*

Vancouver, Canada April 2023 - today

<u>Wear audio recorder</u>: An app for reporters, students and teachers to easily record and manage their audio recordings. Allows you to synchronize your device with Wear OS and an Android application. Over 1 million downloads and over 50,000 monthly active users.

Result:

- * Improved stability: crash free weekly increased from 98.5 to 99.3
- * Rating improvement: application rating increased from 4.11 to 4.2
- * User growth: user growth from 36,000 to 50,000
- * Innovations: users received new functionality "Trash with auto deletion" and marked icons and badges for people with disabilities

Employee on internship *QA Engineer (remote)*

London, Great Britain may 2023 - june 2023

<u>Date AI</u> – приложение, которое поможет вам создать идеальный профиль для знакомств и создать идеальное первое сообщение для вашего партнёра, используя ИИ. Android. Результат работы:

- Написаны требования, чек-лист и баг-репорты

Education

- <u>Functional software testing</u> by Artsiom Rusau (2023)
- Moscow State Law Academy, faculty of law (2009-2011)

Skills & Other

Android Studio
Youtrack, ClickUp, Qase, TestIT | Jira, TestRail - Basic
MySQL, MongoDB
Postman. SoapUI
Charles. Fiddler Classic
HTML5, CSS3
Git Bash, VSC
Chrome DevTools